Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Moving Images Collection, ca. 1928-2001 UA.Film.Video
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sports, I.
  - Basketball, 2.
    - Video
      - Men's, 194 items
        - Pitt Pre-season Basketball Special, December 1, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 5:30-6:00pm (Box 32, Video 656)
        - Pitt vs. St. Johns, January 19, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 35 Millimeter Tape Tape 1 of 2 (Box 32, Video 661)
        - Pitt vs. Syracuse #3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA-20 Needs Case (Box 32, Video 662)
        - Pitt Basketball Headshots, January 3, 1995; Betacam SP (Box 32, Video 669)
        - Sean Miller On Johnny Carson, April 9, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU-18 (Box 34, Video 705)
        - Pitt vs. Syracuse, January 8, 1992; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 35, Video 718)
        - Pitt vs. Syracuse, January 8, 1992; Betacam Sp 90 Minute Broadcast Videocassette Tape 2 of ? (Box 35, Video 714)
        - "Pitt vs. Syracuse" - Tape #2, February 7, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 36, Video 722)
        - "Pitt vs. Syracuse" - Tape #3, February 7, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of ? (Box 36, Video 724)
        - Charles Smith / L.A. Clippers (ATTN: Larry Eldridge / University of Pittsburgh), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic (Box 39, Video 778)
        - Pitt vs Villanova, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 788)
        - Pittsburgh at Rutgers (1/25/98) / Pittsburgh vs. Providence (2/21/98), January 25, 1998 AND February 21, 1998; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 789)
        - Pittsburgh vs. Boston College (2/8/98) / Pittsburgh vs. Villanova (2/10/98), February 8, 1998 AND February 10, 1998; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 790)
        - Pitt vs. St. Francis / Pitt vs. Georgetown / Pitt vs. West Virginia - 1992-1993, VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 791)
        - Pitt v. Miami (TV), February 28, 1995; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 39, Video 799)
        - Pitt Syracuse 2nd Half #1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 39, Video 809)
        - Panther BB With Ralph Willard (1/31/98) / Syracuse at Pittsburgh (2/1/98) / Pittsburgh at West Virginia (2/3/98), January 31, 1998 AND February 1, 1998 AND February 3, 1998; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 810)
        - Pitt vs. Seton Hall / Pitt vs. St. Johns, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 812)
        - Pittsburgh at Georgetown (2/17/98) / Pittsburgh vs. Villanova (2/24/98), February 17, 1998 AND February 24, 1998; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 815)
        - Ralph Willard - Live Mic (Pitt vs. Praine View), December 3, ????; Betacam SP 5 Minute Needs Case (Box 39, Video 824)
        - :30 1990-91 Arena / Bball Ticket Spot - "POWER", unknown; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 40, Video 846)
        - Pitt vs Penn State - Men's Basketball, Civic Arena Promo, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 40, Video 847)
        - "Pitt Basketball Footage for TV Spot", unknown; Betacam SP 10 Minute (Box 40, Video 854)
        - "Pitt Basketball Head Shots" (91-92 Season), unknown; Betacam SP (Box 40, Video 855)
        - Pitt Basketball Video, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 40, Video 856)
        - Pitt Basketball - "Ready for the 90's?", unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 889)
        - Sean Miller, unknown; Betacam SP (Box 41, Video 890)
        - Pitt Men's Basketball - 1992-1993 Headshots - Pittsburgh, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 42, Video 901)
        - Basketball Highlights - 1993-1994 - Tape 1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 42, Video 902)
        - Basketball Highlights 1993-1994 - Tape 2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 42, Video 921)
        - 1994-1995 Basketball Recruiting - Ralph Willard (Edit Master), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 42, Video 903)
        - 24 WKYU-TV - Western Kentucky University - Shots of Ralph Willard, Former Coach, March 31, 1994; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 42, Video 905)
        - Pitt Basketball, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 42, Video 912)
        - Pitt vs. Connecticut, January 31, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of 2 (Box 42, Video 915)
        - Coaches vs. Cancer Spot, unknown; Betacam SP (Box 43, Video 938)
        - 97-98 Pittsburgh Panthers - Men's Basketball Headshots, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 45, Video 1041)
        - Harmaville Hoops - Half Hour Wrap Up Show, May 14, 1994; VHS T-120 (Box 47, Video 1076)
        - Basketball - Pitt at Georgetown (L 76-57) / Highlights - WTAE news, January 11, 1989; VHS (Box 47, Video 1078)
        - "Pitt vs Georgetown" - (1990-91 Basketball Season), unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 47, Video 1083)
        - Basketball - Pitt at Georgetown (2/20/91) (L 97-81) / Providence at Pitt (1/12/91), February 20, 1991 AND January 12, 1991; VHS T-120 (Box 47, Video 1085)
        - 1991-92 Big East Basketball Seniors Video, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 47, Video 1088)
        - "Pitt vs. Seton Hall", unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 47, Video 1090)
        - Pitt Basketball Headshots, January 3, 1995; Betacam SP (Box 48, Video 1102)
        - Pitt vs St Johns, January 9, 1988; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast Tape 2 of 2 (Box 48, Video 1110)
        - Pitt vs. Duquesne, January 11, 1988; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast Tape 2 of 2 (Box 48, Video 1112)
        - Pitt - Syracuse Basketball (Reel #1), January 11, 1986; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast Tape 1 of ? (Box 49, Video 1117)
        - Pitt - Syracuse Basketball (Reel #2), January 11, 1986; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast Tape 2 of ? (Box 49, Video 1120)
        - University of Pittsburgh - Pitt vs. Georgetown Promo (Master), January 10, 1992; 1 Inch Videotape (Box 50, Video 1126)
        - Pitt Hoops Show #2 - "Team in Transition" (Master), January 28, 1989; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast (Box 51, Video 1141)
        - Basketball Headshots - 1991-92 Pitt, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Needs Case (Box 48, Video 1103)
        - Pittsburgh @ Syracuse, February 16, 2000; Betacam SP 30 Minute Michael Molinari (Box 3, Video 68)
        - "Big East Basketball Coaches", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR20 (Box 1, Video 463)
        - Ben Howland Interview - Time Coded - TRT is about 15:00, unknown; VHS Approximately 15:00 TRT (Box 9, Video 162)
        - University of Pittsburgh Alabama Relays, March 25, 2000; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 3 (Box 4, Video 71)
        - University of Pittsburgh Alabama Relays, March 25, 2000; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 3 (Box 4, Video 72)
        - University of Pittsburgh Alabama Relays, March 25, 2000; Betacam SP 10 Minute Tape 3 of 3 (Box 17, Video 299)
        - Dub--Pitt Basketball, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA20 (Box 1, Video 460)
        - Basketball Recruiting Tape, unknown; VHS T120 (Box 4, Video 211)
        - "Basketball Recruiting Video" Music Only, unknown; Betacam SP 60 Minute AMPEX 298 (Box 10, Video 179)
        - Larry Eldrige Edit Master "Shot for the Top", unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 9, Video 280)
        - USC Part 2, unknown; VHS T120 (Box 4, Video 326)
      - Women's, 55 items
        This series contains 55 videos pertaining to Pitt Women's basketball, mostly from the 1990s. These videos mostly consist of game footage, including footage from the 1996 NCAA Women's Basketball Championship.
        - 1989 John Hancock Bowl Presentation, VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 268)
        - 1997 Women's Alumni Basketball Game, Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 16, Video 280)
        - Lori Johnson Highlights, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 16, Video 279)
        - Pittsburgh vs Syracuse Women's Basketball, December 7, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 48:07 Tape 1 of 3 (Box 16, Video 270)
        - Pittsburgh vs Syracuse Women's Basketball, December 7, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 4:28 (Box 16, Video 271)
        - Pittsburgh vs Syracuse Women's Basketball, December 7, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 58:56 Tape 3 of 3 (Box 16, Video 272)
        - Womens Basketball Pitt vs St. John's, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 264)
        - Womens Basketball Pitt vs St. John's, unknown; Betacam SP Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 273)
        - Womens Basketball Pitt vs St. John's, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 274)
        - Womens Basketball Pitt vs St. John's, unknown; Betacam SP Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 275)
        - Pitt Womens Basketball Pre-Game Show For Seniors Last Home Game, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 16, Video 276)
        - Women's Basketball Spot (:45), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 16, Video 278)
        - Women's Basketball Spot (:45), unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 16, Video 260)
        - Women's Basketball vs Connecticut First Half, February 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 265)
        - Women's Basketball vs Connecticut Second Half, February 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 263)
        - University of Pittsburgh Women's Basketball vs Uconn (1998-99), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 16, Video 266)
        - University of Pittsburgh Women's Basketball vs Uconn (98-99), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 16, Video 267)
        - Women's Basketball vs. Boston College 1st Half, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 262)
        - Womens Basketball vs Boston College 2nd Half, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 261)
        - Women's Basketball Pitt vs Boston College Part 2 of, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 16, Video 258)
        - Women"s Basketball Pitt vs. W. Virginia, February 9, 1997; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 16, Video 259)
        - Big East Women's Hoop - Pittsburgh at Seton Hall, February 13, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? (Box 16, Video 348)
        - Pitt vs. Penn State Women's Basketball, December 6, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of 2 (Box 16, Video 350)
        - Pitt Womens Basketball, November 30, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20BQ Tape 1 of ? (Box 16, Video 353)
        - Pitt Womens Basketball, November 30, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20BQ Tape 3 of ? (Box 16, Video 351)
        - Women's Basketball 1993 Seniors, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 16, Video 347)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs. St. John's, February 13, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 35 Millimeter Tape Tape 1 of 3 (Box 32, Video 635)
        - Pitt Womens Basketball - Tape 2, November 30, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20s SP Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 45, Video 1039)
        - Pitt Women's Basketball, November 30, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20BQ (says Tape #2, but is really Tape 3 of ?) (Box 32, Video 657)
        - Pitt Women's - Uconn 96 Tournament, 1996; VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 793)
        - Jonna Huemrich?, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 39, Video 822)
        - Pitt Women DUB, unknown; Betacam SP L-500 Needs Case (Box 39, Video 823)
        - University of Pittsburgh Women's Basketball Headshots - 1997-1998, unknown; Betacam Sp 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 40, Video 839)
        - 1997-98 Women's Basketball Headshots (COPY), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 40, Video 851)
        - Women's B-Ball Headshots - Master 1997-98 (8-30-2004 DOES NOT PLAY), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 40, Video 852)
        - Lady Panther Seniors, February 25, 1995; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 40, Video 860)
        - Women's B-Ball - Pitt vs. St. John's, February 13, 1992; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA-60 Tape 2 of 3 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 1004)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs. St. John's, February 13, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60HG Tape 3 of 3 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 969)
        - Pitt Women's Basketball vs. Boston College, February 19, 1992; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60HG Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 971)
        - Pitt Women's Basketball vs. Boston College, February 19, 1992; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60HG Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 970)
        - WB-Ball #1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 44, Video 988)
        - WB-Ball #2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 44, Video 987)
        - WB-Ball #3, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 44, Video 990)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt-PC 2nd 1/2 (vs Providence, No Audio), unknown; Betacam SP 60 Minute Needs Case (Box 44, Video 1002)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt-PC Overtime (vs Providence), unknown; Betacam SP 60 Minute Needs Case (Box 44, Video 1013)
        - Big East Women's Basketball - Pitt at Seton Hall - Reel 1, February 13, 1994; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 44, Video 1006)
        - Big East Women's Hoop - Pittsburgh at Seton Hall, February 13, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA-60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 44, Video 1005)
        - Pitt vs. Penn State Women's Basketball, December 6, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of 2 (Box 44, Video 1009)
        - Pittsburgh Panther Women's Basketball - 1999-2000, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 44, Video 1012)
        - 1998-99 Pittsburgh Women's Basketball Highlight Video, unknown; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 1016)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs Georgetown #1 (Lori Johnson), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 45, Video 1043)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs Georgetown #2 (Lori Johnson), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 45, Video 1046)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs Georgetown #3 (Lori Johnson), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 45, Video 1044)
        - Women's Basketball - Pitt vs Boston College Pt 1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 45, Video 1047)
        - "Pitt vs St. John's", January 21, 1989; VHS T-120 (Box 48, Video 1101)
        - "Ready for the 80s" (The Story of the Pitt Basketball Team), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 892)
      - Men's and Women's, 2 items
        This section contains two videos, each of which contains footage of both the Pitt Men's and Women's basketball teams. One video contains headshots from both teams, and the other video contains game footage from both teams.
        - Pitt Basketball 1993-1994 Pitt Mens/Womens Basketball Headshots, Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 4, Video 199)
        - Pitt vs. BG Men- December 1995 / Pitt vs. Penn State Women December 1995, VHS T-120 (Box 42, Video 911)
  - Football, 3.
    This subseries contains over 1,600 film and videos of football footage, much of which pertains to the Pitt football program. There is much game footage of Pitt's offense and defense, respectively, from the 1990s, as well as much footage of bowl games, interviews with as well as profiles of prominent figures, such as Tony Dorsett and Mike Ditka, pregame shows, etc. This subseries also includes much footage from football games with rivals such as Penn State, West Virginia, and Syracuse.
    - Film, 957 items
      This section contains nearly 1,000 football game films from 1931 through 1988. Many of these films break down Pitt's offense, defense, or kicking during a given component of the game (quarters, halves, etc.). This includes multiple bowl games.
      - 1932 #1 Ohio State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 1)
      - 1935 Carnegie Tech vs. Pitt, unknown; 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 5/6/5 (Box 42, Reel 1025)
      - 1937 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 1 Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 872)
      - 1937 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 868)
      - 1939 #1 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 2)
      - 1939 #2 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 3)
      - 1941 #1 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 8)
      - 1941 #1 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 7)
      - 1941 #2 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 1939; 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 4)
      - 1941 #2 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 871)
      - 1941 #3 Purdue vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 5)
      - 1941 #4 Carnegie Tech vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 9)
      - 1941 #5 Fordham vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 6)
      - 1941 #6 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 11)
      - 1942 #1 Indiana vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 14)
      - 1943 #1 Great Lakes vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 12)
      - 1943 #2 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 13)
      - 1945 #1 Temple vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 15)
      - 1946 #1 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 1 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 17)
      - 1946 #1 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 18)
      - 1947 #1 Michigan vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 16)
      - 1947 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 873)
      - 1948 #1 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 1079)
      - 1948-1949 #2 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 1 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 20)
      - 1948-1949 #2 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 21)
      - 1948-1949 #2 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 22)
      - 1949 #1 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 66)
      - 1949 #2 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1067)
      - 1949 #3 Ohio State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 19)
      - 1950 #1 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 69)
      - 1950 #3 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1068)
      - 1950 #4 Rice vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 70)
      - 1950 #5 Miami vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 67)
      - 1950 #6 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1069)
      - 1950 #7 Ohio State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 71)
      - 1951 #1 Indiana vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 72)
      - 1952 #1 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 68)
      - 1952 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 73)
      - 1952 #3 Indiana vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 64)
      - 1952 #4 Oklahoma vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 63)
      - 1952 #5 Ohio State vs. Pitt (1st half), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/5 (Box 42, Reel 1043)
      - 1953 #1 Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 65)
      - 1953 #3 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 76)
      - 1953 #4 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 77)
      - 1954 #1 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 81)
      - 1954 #2 Ohio State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 82)
      - 1954 #3 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 74)
      - 1954 #4 Southern California vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 29)
      - 1954 #5 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 75)
      - 1955 #1 California vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 83)
      - 1955 #2 Oklahoma vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 84)
      - 1955 #3 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 78)
      - 1955 #4 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1063)
      - 1955 #5 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 79)
      - 1955 #7 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1064)
      - 1955 #8 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 80)
      - 1956 #1 Pitt vs. Oregon, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 24)
      - 1956 #2 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 26)
      - 1956 #3 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 27)
      - 1956 #3A Hilites, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 10)
      - 1956 #4 California vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 28)
      - 1956 #5 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 23)
      - 1956 #6 Minnesota vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 25)
      - 1956 Sugar Bowl, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/5 (Box 42, Reel 1007)
      - 1957 #1 Army vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 32)
      - 1957 #2 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 33)
      - 1957 #3 West Virginia vs. Pitt (1st Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 42)
      - 1957 #3 West Virginia vs. Pitt (2nd Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 43)
      - 1957 #3 West Virginia vs. Pitt (3rd Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 44)
      - 1957 #3 West Virginia vs. Pitt (4th Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 45)
      - 1957 #4 Hilites, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 41)
      - 1958 #1 Michigan State, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 89)
      - 1958 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 90)
      - 1958 #3 UCLA vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 88)
      - 1958 #4 Nebraska vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 86)
      - 1958 #5 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 91)
      - 1958 #6 Holy Cross vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 92)
      - 1958 Season: Holy Cross vs. Pitt, Army vs. Pitt, Syracuse vs. Pitt, Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 406)
      - 1959 #1 UCLA vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 87)
      - 1959 #2 Duke vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 93)
      - 1959 #3 Southern California vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 94)
      - 1959 #4 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 95)
      - 1959 #5 Marquette (First Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 85)
      - 1960 #1 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 35)
      - 1960 #2 Michigan State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 30)
      - 1960 #3 Texas Christian vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 47)
      - 1960 #4 Miami vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 31)
      - 1960 #5 UCLA vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 48)
      - 1960 #6 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 46)
      - 1960 #7 Oklahoma vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room
      - 1960 #8 Army vs. Pitt (2nd Quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 40)
      - 1960 #9 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 34)
      - 1961 #1 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 4/8/4 (Box 42, Reel 1070)
      - 1961 #2 Miami vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 97)
      - 1961 #3 Southern California vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 98)
      - 1961 #4 Washington vs. Pitt (1st and 2nd Quarters), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 99)
      - 1961 #4 Washington vs. Pitt (3rd and 4th Quarters), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 96)
      - 1961 #5 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 100)
      - 1961 #6 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 101)
      - 1961 #6 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 867)
      - 1961 #7 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 102)
      - 1961 #8 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 103)
      - 1961 Spring Game, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 864)
      - 1961 Baylor vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 866)
      - 1962 #1 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/1 (Box 42, Reel 51)